SAH KWADWO DANIEL

STUDENT

PHONE: +233 54 514 3000 EMAIL: danielsah118@mail.com ADDRESS: TECHIMAN



PROFILE

Resourceful Front End Web Developer bringing in-depth knowledge of latest technology trends to produce a clean website design.

Experience handling complex HTML and CSS coding, design and extensions to meet organization's front-facing internet needs.

Detail-oriented collaboration with others to define project expectations and demand.



SKILLS

COMPUTER SKILLS

Microsoft Office

Programming

HTML

Bootstrap

CSS proficiency

Javascript programming

Search Engine Optimization

Responsive Web Development

PERSONAL SKILLS

Leadership and training

Creativity

Planning and Forecasting

Management

Able to work under pressure



WORK EXPERIENCE

FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER

2018 - Present

Self Employed, Techiman

- Wrote clean HTML and CSS code, integrating design, extensions and third-party apps according to web development plans
- Tested site compatibility across multiple browsers and devices, uncovering and debugging issues and addressing inconsistencies

MANAGER'S ASSISTANT

2020-2021

Sigina Filtered Drinking Water Company, Techiman

• Ran errands to support daily needs of management

SALES AGENT 2017-2020

Sie Kwasi Enterprise, Techiman

- Provide superior service to customers by quickly and courteously responding to requests, inquiries, suggestions and concern
- Offered each customer top-notch, personal service to boost sales and customer satisfaction.



EDUCATION

BSC. COMPUTER SCIENCE

2021 - Present

University of Energy and Natural Resources, Sunyani Computer science

WASSCE 2014 - 2017

Armed Forces Senior High Technical School, Kumasi General Science

BECE 2011- 2014

Pentecost Preparatory School, Techiman